her name in the temples of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight
crowds came running just to see the flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands
where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom in the same breath
burns gold, not red
He likes to sit in front of the screen, so I can't see.
Let me see if I, I'm going to try something.
Oh my, there's my tablet, my bedroom, all the way back.
So I can mod from the tablet.
just look I don't know maybe it's always goes birthday today on her birthday
let's try something we see mmm and happy birthday ghost everyone which goes
happy birthday I don't know if he's here right now I hope you guys can hear me
okay my microphone on mmm okay let's see
I'm trying to set it cool, oh here it is.
Can we do this?
Five, four, let's see.
There's a goal created. It's a reasonable goal, I think.
And if nobody wants to, we'll do other stuff.
There. These are my Dahmer sunglasses. I got them on T-Move for like three dollars or something.
But I think they look pretty good.
Yeah, I always give away too much of it. Hey, Sponky, how are you? Sorry, Mr. Panel, I was sleeping.
I hope you had a good one.
Everyone's good.
I'll just try to drink the smirnoff tonight.
Smirnoff, smash.
I don't know.
Probably should have got some more alcohol.
Maybe it'll put me in a better mood.
Shooting range glasses, yeah.
So we'll have a positive night tonight.
I'll have my, I think I'm almost out of the sentence.
Let's see if it works. This is my last one. Yeah, it's my last one of these ones, so.
This is my favorite one out of them. It smells really good.
Oh, what's Kiddy's name? This is, this is Tricks right here. That's Mr. Tricks.
These are Tricks. I got Lola running around. Lenore's just in here.
The black cat. Rudy's right on the, the, the, the
I like playing with them since a little bit
Yeah, yeah tricks because I had another cat
His brother we had so Lola gave birth last year to five kittens
And I only have tricks left but he had a kind of a twin named magic
But magic had all white magic just had his paws white
And tricks has like white arms. We have magic and tricks and they were like little
inseparable but
Yeah
Five cats there's five in here five cat. Oh, what does this do? Let me see I have I'm seeing like some kind of
Something just appeared on the screen. I don't know what that was. Okay. I do have like some cool
Settings though I can put on a background real quick visual effects
You're in space, right? Oh, that's
I'm going there.
OK.
Yeah, remember, do you guys remember Magic?
When I started the show, I had Magic.
I had, I think I had Tux, maybe Pi.
They were like little tuxedo cats.
They, yeah, I think Pi was a good number.
Hi, babe.
But you know.
You have a certain amount. They're just gonna have the ones that want to be inside and get along and then there's ones that want to walk around
Okay, oh, you can't see him really well. I'll turn off the background because it kind of hides tricks
See
Hi chicken
There we go
Okay, okay
Hi everybody, how are we guys doing trying to look at I'm sorry if I hate summer
How are you sweetheart? I'm sorry if I miss any of the chats. I'm gonna be in I'm gonna try to be in a
Good mood tonight and just stay positive. You know, it's been
It's like it's like if I could find my VR controllers that would probably make me pretty happy, but
It's frustrating because I just had them the other day. I know I didn't
You know take him out of the house or anything, but I put him somewhere and I I'm searched the house
Yeah, you remember magic and tricks. What's the name of the cult? It's called the cult of psyche or it's called of the cult of Orion
Maybe that's my AI
Or it's just called psyche awakens whatever not really cool
It's kind of like you have some like this this I had this co-host named hi before
Apparently she's not a big fan of mine anymore I made a cute little on snapchat. It's called or something snapchat
Yeah, I think it's snapchat. They had these little filters and they're she was my only friends there
And so they just take your little avatar and like they put it together
I thought I was I made like a couple like little cute things. I thought was cute. Oh
I get these messages posted on my
my post, my wall, and personal message.
Oh, do you not use my image?
I feel like you're using me, blah, blah.
I was like, all I did was send it to her.
I didn't, it was just like,
it wasn't supposed to be any kind of like,
trying to like, you know,
make money off of her.
I don't know what she's thinking,
but she's like, feeling like being really snippy with me.
But anyway
What was like it was a story about pie like yeah, oh, yeah, she was like, oh you're just you're using brainwashing tactics on your chat
Let me put you quit being a coho. She was like accusing me of being a cult leader
I just kind of like ran with it ran with that. I thought it was kind of funny
You know if I have a cult of the cult of one, it's just basically me and the cult
Leader of myself I wouldn't I wouldn't want to
Consignuate to anybody else. This is just tobacco whether what I'm out of we've
I'm spoke. Yeah, the bomb because this I just have these left. It's not like a little can't smoke those anymore
So I just tip up into the back over the bomb
I practice greekie. Okay, so that's like that's like some kind of something with voodoo or voodoo, right?
Yeah
Trying to get away from these sharks
You know, I heard some interesting things
There's a lot of aquatic references to like, you know negative things like you know sharks
I mean sometimes sharks are equated to lawyers and stuff like that
Lawyers or just people that will like the smell blood and they just jump in an attack, right?
so I've dealt with sharks also there's the whale and
There's a tarot card or it's actually a Oracle deck and they have a whale on it and it's like
I like this definition of it the best.
It's like making a big deal out of nothing
or like, you know, being worried,
having this big worry about nothing,
that's what a whale is.
But some people think, oh, whale,
there's some kind of reference to some whale
floating in the middle space.
It's supposed to be some really sinister meaning to it.
If anyone knows, you do practice, do you do it?
Okay, cool.
If anyone knows like the other definition of whale,
what people are meaning when they say,
oh, what is, imagine a whale in the middle of space,
like it has some sinister meaning to it,
but I don't know.
No one ever told me so if you can you can let me know what that is and sorry if I have to check messages, too
I'm sorry if I'm a little behind. Okay stargazer. You have a blessed night, too
I didn't mean to like I'm sorry guys if I don't acknowledge or seek the chat does go fast
What is this thing right here?
Lucid mode is on. Oh, what does that mean?
What is it? And I have them
Lucid mode is on what is I don't know what that is. Okay, there's just new stuff appearing. I'm still learning guys
This uh, oh here. What is this one do picture and picture? Okay, that does picture and picture
Okay, I don't know what lucid mode is but okay, we're trying to some new stuff. Let me see and
Okay, I'm getting my settings done. Thank you stargazer
Am I taking new members absolutely sure all you to do is click on the little I think if you're on a
Android you can click on the little
Three dots or the little dollar sign and it should say sign up for a member
It's not my member. It's ghost birthday ghost birthday. My birthday is in January, but it is ghosts birthday
That's there's a little picture of a ghost on it
Yeah
Hi everybody
Yeah, so yeah, there you go. It's like, uh, let me see, I think this one is for the, yeah.
And guys, you know, there are a lot of, especially, I put most of the stuff that is like, if I get like a copyrighted or it gets age-restricted, I keep those members only.
So probably the more, the more, uh, shocking or...
You know episodes you'll find in the members and also, you know, I'll do like a long reading per month for a member
You just have to let me know and stuff and I
Want to give good value to it is $5. Also, there's emojis that only members can use if a member like
You know, I'm a member actually so I can like probably use the emojis for
Gonna show you the emojis. Here's what they look like for members
have like 12 up right now something like that 1 2 3 4 I 14 of them up so there's a special
member emojis I'm a member of my own channel so there's a troll there's a goddess evil
Help me, and another goat, there's one goat, there's a goat and a ghost, yeah.
I've worked really hard to make sure they were cool, original, and unique.
Anyway, I think that you also have your names highlighted, so a lot of people want to say, oh well.
You don't read my post or anything. I'll try to say to do a shout out for members like, you know, let me see the members today
Okay, so me
There is
Let's see just me so far
also
Okay, it looks like I am the only
member
Of my channel right now, but that's okay. It's okay
You know
Life sometimes has ups and downs, right? Okay. I might be in a down, but you know
Sometimes with down the only way to go is up
but
Yeah, and I did I mean I did sponsor a lot of the memberships last month and so when they expire
So I understand why I don't have many your sharks
I appreciate any donation, any super chats, also if you want to have your name recognized
or recognized, I will read your super chats unless they're like Renault against TOS or
like attacking somebody, which sometimes they are.
It's okay, you know
Yeah, I mean, that's what the membership is. It's like, you know, the paid paid tier and so that's why there's no a
Reading and stuff involved with it. So but I understand that not everybody can afford
you know
afford one and so
No big deal
Maybe I'll do it like a 99 cents here
With like without and I'll just have the emojis on it. Maybe I don't know
It's me the idea. Do we get three meals a day?
I ate a spinach
Florentine bagel today
And I have a smirnoff
I think I've kind of exhausted my food budget for the week, but I
Do eat every day so
That's what ramen noodles look for right?
The cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the cat, the
Yeah, no worries.
So I did set a goal for like $10 tonight.
It's like if there's $5, $2 super chats, they'll do an open panel.
I think that's, if I got your idea wrong, I'm sorry, I thought it was.
Yeah, I could talk to, I'll talk to AI about it.
What have I been eating like I basically my treat is like
Using them at getting a McDonald's deal on the app. I think I have free something for other coming up
Maybe I'll maybe I'll stop and go get McDonald's later today. I just have to walk a few blocks
You know, you know, my bike is like
My bike
My neighbors help me fix the battery of it and then as soon as I fix the battery
I like wrote it and then I had the the lock tangled in into it somehow the lock it
basically broke the back
Some of the stuff in the back and my neighbor was like it has moved and I was like can you help me with it?
And I already asked you know they help me twice with it
And she's like oh, she's like just take it to like a bike repair or something so
Maybe I'll be able to do that someday
Anyway, let's see
Just closing some tabs, I'm sorry
Yeah, the bikes out of commission until I can well first of all I need some good
I need to like, you know, I'm afraid to take it to a bike shop because it has the lock
The locks on opening it's a numerical lock. It's tangled in there
And so if I go to a bike shop, it looks like I stole the bike first of all
And so I asked if you take it like they had a
Like some kind of like things that you know the pliers it whatever those the white thing those cutters might ask my neighbors
No, she never really got back to me about that and then um I
Know I don't think it's like that much. I think once that's gone. They can change me back on
I think it will just probably take a couple screws
But I know I asked enough of them, I think so
Yeah, I was gonna write it. Yeah, I don't think it will get me to Florida anymore
I don't know if she wants to see me anymore or still see me too. I was at her chat the other day and she
was cool
But I you know, she's been out
Count for a while. Hey Rouge
Hi babe
Yeah, I mean it's like even if you know all I consider is support is like people being here
You know, it's like you're here
Some people are nice enough to use the nightbot commands and stuff like that
I don't know how effective they've they've really been I mean the nightbot commands not the people not the people but the nightbot commands
seems like I
Don't know I understand I've had enough things said about me. I understand if people believe them because
There are things are repeated often enough, right? And
Somebody kind of controversial one said a lie repeated often enough becomes the truth
And so when it's constantly being called a grifter a scammer
you know
I'm sure it dampens the enthusiasm of donating but all I can say is that those words are thrown around
There's nothing ever to back them up, you know back. There's one of the first it kind of started with us, you know when
when somebody donated fifty dollars to have Alex removed immediately and
Or Alex removed permanently and then I had him
I know I had him on for like a couple minutes minutes a few weeks later
And so it's like oh you scammed you scammed you scammed so I just give a full refund for it
So that's scamming I don't
It's like I've always given refunds if I didn't look to my end of the bargain and fortunately
it's only been a couple of times, but people see that it probably bothers me so they just
will repeat it again and again and again and again.
It's just repeated every day.
Just like now it's like I have people saying I have HIV that's repeated every day.
I'm not the only one, but it's more like just hurtful, but, you know, I can't really do
anything about it.
If I bring attention to it, I'm wrong, if I don't bring attention to it, I'm wrong.
So it's like some things you can't win, but it's okay.
Not unsexually active as me. It would probably be very rare that you know, I get in I wouldn't catch anything. I
I'm always been pretty
Phobic of like, you know diseases and stuff like me myself catching a disease especially growing up in the 80s and seeing all these people
people dying of that in the 80s
And so I never was really into like, you know
Promiscuity or anything. I'm not a promiscuous person. Even if there was no diseases or anything
I don't think I'd be a very promiscuous person. I really
would love
and like I did Disney kind of programming was like
Someday my prince will come
very
Waiting for the white horse right the guy on the white horse
Probably never come but
Yeah, it's kind of like it is sad and it's like it meant and it's like also like I didn't realize like
How bad the homophobia would be and it's like it's okay like I did I dealt with that in all my life, right?
Or you know basically since I came out of the closet when I was pretty young. I
Support a family
But I didn't
Think you would be so homophobic as it is in this community
With some people I know I know some people aren't and it's like whatever
Actually, I had like there's actually that one you know a couple like two
I can just think of two gay people, you know out of everybody like I can think of like or maybe three like
No, there's bikes, you know that are bisexual and that's a guy
But I only say who they are because I don't want them even if they are out of their closet and you know, whatever
I don't want them to experience the homophobia and the negativity, but yeah, it's like like
it like for example like I said like any any guy that is donated and so it's just I know
men are very discouraged from donating oh they'll be called gay they'll be say oh you're
trying to you're in love with them or something and it's you know nobody has them.
I don't think I've had a gay donor
But
Yeah, I don't want to dwell on the negativity. I'm sorry if I you know, I shouldn't even bring some of this stuff up
I just like I'll just say what how I'm feeling. That's like I can't really
Change myself to where I'm like just change my personality where I don't say what I'm feeling
I'm like very much open book and tell everything. I even told so many negative things about me. I've talked about my drug history
I've talked about
I'm talking about embarrassing things, I'm talking about being scammed, and I was like okay well I can help people if I tell my story.
It seems like it didn't really help people, it just gave people an opening to attack me more.
But you know what, I have good people here, I'm not going to focus on the haters and stuff.
I probably need to deal with things in a better way.
It's okay, Ms. Liz, I don't, I don't, I don't, I,
it was, I don't know if you know the story about, you know,
the, I don't even want to say their name, you know,
there's a little group that just went to attack me and stuff
and say terrible things about me.
They started a lot of the rumors
or like a lot of the abuse harassment.
Every time I bring them up to the exam harassing them, and so I'm just not gonna acknowledge them anymore
And that thing is like I liked a lot of people in this group. I
Welcome them here. I let them on town. I
You know people said don't you shouldn't let you shouldn't do that they're they're only here to hurt you and
I knew that they were in a certain way, but
I always like to think that I can change people's minds about me
or that people that really get to know me will actually like me.
But that's not always true.
Always true.
But I don't know, you might have gotten,
so I basically, people that were associated with them in a big way.
I unmodded just because
Even if I like you and stuff like that, I just you know, I just was like
I don't know it's kind of hard to know who to trust sometimes
Plus people were hiding people like I had over a hundred people hit it
And so I had to unhide everybody and then it was like then the trolling got really really bad
And it's our reality. It's just
whoo
But yeah
But if I get to know you and I you know
I mean not just you I mean anybody if I if I know if I get to like, you know, really know you
happy to like, you know, I
Just need to know people have my my back and my side and especially like in a lot of other places right now that I'm being discussed and shows
being done about me and it's like
Don't know. I just like there's not a hate train. I would want to jump on even if I didn't like somebody. I'm not gonna go
Start a panel about them and stuff like that, you know, I have called some people out on their behavior toward me or whatever, but I
Haven't made it all about them nor have I slandered anybody all I do is tell exactly what happened
my side of the story and stuff
but
Then again, like I defend myself. Oh, you're defensive. It must be true if I don't defend myself
Oh, you're just letting them, you know, you must be true because you're not defending yourself, right?
It's like I'm getting putting all these catch 22 situations where it's like I just can't win with it
so
I choose like lesser of two evil sometimes. Hey, rude
My baby
Yeah, there are amazing people here. The amazing people are why I keep it. I keep it
Going like you coming back out or I would I would have quit
There's like no if there's nobody
Or if I was like if I was just being looked at like a little cow, which is like even if it was a little cow like you know
Not not even out if I was because I'm not but if I was considered that by people
There's a lot you guys don't know about me. Like there's a lot I I do keep private, you know
But there's a lot of like
Good things that I keep hitting about me, right and I have like I do have a great
Support system I do have like a lot of really great people around me. I'm still here guys, right? I'm still
So
I have a, you know, basically, I wouldn't want people to know, like, what people think
about me.
Like, people I love because they would be very hurt, you know.
And so I try to keep things separated, right?
Because I don't want to unleash...
I have...
I do have, like, you know, big dogs that can come out and defend me.
I'm not calling them out.
I'm not asking them for help.
They're not really into YouTube or the shows, but they would be hurt if they knew what was
really going on, but so I don't want to, I don't want to bring anybody else down.
Let's see, yeah, I know, I know you're talking about too, I know you're talking about I think
Yeah, I mean it's like and I think some people might have their like their own
Demons and stuff like that in their own. I
Don't want to call out people
You know like that, but I
Don't know I try to be try to be nice
And then it gets me in trouble, but it's just being even being nice
But no, I'm not a victim guys because it's like, you know what? I I'm able to handle
Handle these things. I'm just kind of
I'm kind of at a low and then
Kind of makes things a little bit worse. I need to get to a
Higher point and then when I'm actually happy
It's like this stuff doesn't bother me when I'm like and I'm at a low
It affects me more and that's like I shouldn't it's just how it is and but still and I should not be going on
online sometimes
But I'm feeling that way
but
Again, I want to stay consistent and I want to be here for everybody that needs me so
But yeah
So I guess thank you, He-Man. I know you care. I know He-Man's been here from the beginning, you know,
Jamie, Summer, Bita, even though some people get frustrated with me sometimes and, you know,
you know, they're kind enough to tell me their truth and their perspective and,
you know, I try to see their perspective. But, you know,
You don't always see what's going on with me in my personal life, even though I show as much as I can
You know
Of course, I need to improve in a lot of ways
Wow, my people please thing. Oh, so what's it called? It's called like the human magnet syndrome versus like I'm an empath and so I
Kind of attract sometimes
Dark triad people or some of my psychopaths. It's just it's always been how it's been right and it's like and I
Unfortunately for me like I'm attracted to
You know in terms of dating and I can't date because I'm attracted to
To bad to bad guys, you know
So and a dangerous for me, but
It'll be okay and everything will be okay, and I don't want to like come up come on a negative
State of mind, so I'm sorry if I do. I'm just letting you know how I feel
And I can get get beyond it. Okay
Not a cigars, okay
First time out of weed
Okay
Another bar stream, yeah, I had fun at the bar unfortunately like you know, I can't really afford a bar anymore
The drinks are probably like $13 and stuff
I'm doing my best though but you know there's a bar across the street but
also there's music playing inside there and so and also yeah nobody really wanted to talk or anything
40 of clear what is clear yeah there's bronze bird calling me drifter deep sea I don't know I
Ever clear I don't know. I just drink up when I could afford it. I smoke a little bit of pot
You get a couple drinks that I can afford it
I just like excuse me there are things people do like waste people treat me some people
I wouldn't treat another human being like that and it's like I can't even treat them like that
I can't even like or this wouldn't it's not part of my thing to be like cruel
To like say don't donate to this person this person doesn't deserve it this person is a scammer this person's a grifter
There's no evidence. They never have any evidence or proof or like they can say oh they can say oh well Tracy
You know
I don't and I can't even I don't want to bring up the Tracy stuff
But you know but Tracy did you talk to Tracy about it talk to Tracy if she considers me that okay?
How about just ask her if she considers if she considers me that I don't she would tell you no
She would tell you no, and it's like you know, you know, she's been scared away from here, too, so
Go ahead bronzer. Give me the evidence that everyone has the evidence there. What is it? I'm a whack-clout chaser. Yeah, whatever
And you know what, my Bronzebird is mad because, you know, I think he has ghosts, or either
me or ghosts or something like that.
They took him off stage when he went too far, and I was like, I reserve the right to run
my panel like I want to, to kick off people for 10 seconds or 30 seconds if I want to,
or as long as I want, actually.
That's my panel.
Just like, they don't have to have me on their show.
I never been to Vronsburg show, but you know I hear he's a content creator
It's sad like attacking other content creators
Especially because you know we should be like you know
We should understand each other being this together kind of thing, but you know he can say whatever he wants
You don't have mugs, you know what it's like
Hey, no, I've been going like you know, please like you know start bleeding these people
Whether you do or not, it's like they're just gonna come back and you know stronger and stuff like that
I'm not trying to play any kind of victim or anything.
Cloud Chaser, what it was, I mean,
but it really was like,
if you'd be doing some cloud chasing activities,
all I'm doing is just coming on, talking,
and I don't know.
I'm at Cloud Chaser, okay.
Then it's like, it's just names.
It's like, I wanna hear like, you did exactly this.
This is exactly what happened without my own without their own spin on it like their own
It's just it basically it's just attacking
so
But maybe it was a bad idea again my mistake sorry for coming on tonight
I was trying to have a fun panel. I guess nobody wants to do a
Panel or anything, but I do want to say happy birthday ghost
It was a good idea
But you know
Nobody fucks with me anymore. So
Yeah, I'm just gonna be wrapping up the show
For real like this show it's done
So thank you guys for being here. I'm sorry